{"data":[{"question":"___ my socks? \"Yes, I saw them on your bed.\"","a":"Had you seen","b":"Do you see","c":"Have you seen","d":"Would you see","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense: We use the Present Perfect to say that an action happened at an unspecified time before now","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Can I help you, ma'am? \"Yes. I bought this clock here yesterday, but it ___\"","a":"won't work","b":"didn't work","c":"doesn't work","d":"can't work","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Simple present tense: Speakers sometimes use the Simple Present to express the idea that an action is happening or is not happening now. ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Helen ___ her keys in the office so she had to wait until her sister ___ home.","a":"left, had come","b":"has left, comes","c":"had left, would come","d":"had left, came","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Past perfect tense:  expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past\n- Past perfect tense + when\/until simple past tense","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Who is Vivian Cooper? \" ___? I saw you shaking hands with her in front of the bank.\"","a":"Hadn't you met him yet","b":"Don't you meet him yet","c":"Haven't you met him yet","d":"Didn't you meet him yet","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense: We use the Present Perfect to say that an action happened at an unspecified time before now\n+We CAN use the Present Perfect with unspecific expressions such as: ever, never, once, many times, several times, before, so far, already, yet, etc.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Alice, why didn't you come yesterday evening?\" \"I ___, but I had an unexpected visitor.","a":"would","b":"had","c":"did","d":"was going to","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Simple past tense: when you reply to a question, you can use only the auxiliary (do\/did..) and keep the same tense","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Your phone number again? I ___ quite catch it. \"It's 25788578.\"","a":"couldn't","b":"didn't","c":"can't","d":"don't","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple past tense: Use the Simple Past to express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"___ the mini marathon might be put off. \"Yes, it all depends on the weather.\"","a":"I've told","b":"I've been told","c":"I told","d":"I'm told","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense (to say that an action happened at an unspecified time before now)+ Passive voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"As he _________ the survey, Danny ___ asleep.","a":"was reading, fell","b":"read, was falling","c":"read, fell","d":"was reading, was falling","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Use the Past Continuous to indicate that a longer action in the past was interrupted. The interruption is usually a shorter action in the Simple Past. \n+ First blank: Past continuous \n+ Second blank: simple past","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"You don't need to describe that policewoman. I ___ her many times.","a":"have met","b":"had met","c":"meet","d":"met","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense: We use the Present Perfect to say that an action happened at an unspecified time before now","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"I don't think Jim saw me; he ___ into space.","a":"just stared","b":"was just staring","c":"has just stared","d":"had just stared","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Tense of verb \"stared\" agrees with tense of verb \"saw\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"}]}